Guide to the Yale Daily News Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographic negatives used in the publication of the Yale Daily News, 1957-1982; Series I
  - 1981
    - 1981 February 3-25
      - Women's Squash v. Penn, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Swimming v. Penn, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Basketball v. Princeton, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Women's Basketball v. Barnard, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Men's Swimming v. Dartmouth, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Wrestling v. UNH, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Volleyball v. Harvard, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Basketball v. Columbia, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Hockey v. N Eastern, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Women's Basketball, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Swimming Coaches, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Women's Hockey v. Boston State, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Wrestling v. Harvard, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Hockey v. Harvard, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Swimming v. Princeton, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Squash v. Princeton, 1981 February (Box 11, Folder 104)
    - 1981 March 1-29
      - President Giamatti speaking at Davenport, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Half-time award of prize to winner of Florida trip, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Hammond Hall Exhibit, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Play in Silliman, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Pippin, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Black and White, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Measure for Measure, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Set design-JE dramat series, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Ezra Stiles student art, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Girl painting on roof, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Women's Tennis v. Penn, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Basketball v. Holy Cross, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Women's Softball v. Rhode Island, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Women's Lacrosse v. Virginia, 1981 March (Box 11, Folder 105)
    - 1981 April 1-22
      - The Last of Marx Brothers writers, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - The Game 1981, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Soldier's Tale, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Yale Cabaret, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Peter Pan, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Women's Lacrosse, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Men's Lacrosse v. Dartmouth, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Women's Lacrosse v. Cornell, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Men's Crew v. Dartmouth, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Yale-Harvard Track v. Oxford-Cambridge, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Men's Lacrosse v. Princeton, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Baseball v. West Point, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Women's Track, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Men's Lacrosse v. Cornell, 1981 April (Box 11, Folder 106)
    - 1981 August 30 - September 30
      - Frosh- opening day, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 107)
      - Tailgating, warm-up (football game), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 107)
      - Chicago Tribune exhibit, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 107)
      - Will Ruff Jazz Concert, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 107)
      - Yale Cabaret, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 107)
      - Papa Gargushian in Trumbull, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 107)
      - Men's Lacrosse, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 107)
      - Stands At Yale/Brown Football Game, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 107)
      - Men's Lacrosse v. Dartmouth, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 107)
    - 1981 October 5 - December 31
      - Tap Night, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Singing group Tap Night, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Pirates of Penzance and personnel, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Cross Country- Aneky and Coach Steve, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - J.B., 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Columbus Day Parade, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Auditions for The Creation (New Haven kids), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Third World Art and Artists, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Yale Cabaret, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Rosner Shalm (?)- Pierson Dramat, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Once Upon a Mattress (JE), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Hunger Conference - Scott and Space, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Silliman- Feast of Blood, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - A Threepenny Opera, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - (Before game dinner?), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Dartmouth weekend (Giamatti and alumni), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Sleuth, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - How the Other Half Lives- Morse Dramat, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Pirates of Penzance, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Peirson art show, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Yale Cabaret Oklahoma, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Glee Club at Princeton, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Princeton Weekend (stands, etc.), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Yale Cabaret- Dear Liar, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - The Importance of Being Earnest (Stiles), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Albee plays in BK, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Play in Silliman Dramatic Attic- Why Crickets Hide, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - 200 Story- Berkeley Dramat, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Swing- TD review, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Davenport Little Theater, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Big Frosh Dinner (Christmas), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Yale Cabaret, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Volleyball, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Princeton Tailgate, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Women's Squash v. Williams, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Volleyball v. Harvard, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - 1982
    - 1982 January 1 - April 27
      - Glee Club recording at Dwight Hall Chapel, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Student Art Show at AandA, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Yale Art Gallery Exhibit, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Yale Cabaret, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Divorced, Beheaded, Died, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Branford Dramat Play (Dogg's Hamlet), 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Polish poster show/ MFA show, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Vanities in Pierson Common Room, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Play at the Dramat, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Afro-American play, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - MFA Thesis Art Show, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Yale Political Union Ash 800, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Babes in Arms-in Nicholas Chapel, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Home Craft, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Of Mice and Men- JE dining hall, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - 1776 Calhoun dining hall musical, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Connie likes to dance, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Viva, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Tow Trucks, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Whiff tap night and concert, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Trumbull College, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Tap night for secret societies, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Political Union (Stomier), 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Sidewalk Circus, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Joan Ryan Sports, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - April 5, blizzard news, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Yale Charities Auction/ Brotherhood, Oster, Furlowe, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Woyczek dress rehearsal- Davenport, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Beckett one-acts: Branford Dining Hall, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Children's Hour dress rehearsal- Nicholas Chapel, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Earth Day News, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Debate- faculty vs. students, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Basketball, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Ice Sculpture, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Pierson Intramural (Softball), 1982 (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Undated/Miscellaneous Negatives
    - Yale/Harvard Football, undated (Box 12, Folder 110)
    - Yale/UConn Football, undated (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Track and Sport?, undated (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Women's Lib (?) band at Silliman, undated (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Alice in Wonderland, undated (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Basketball, undated (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Football v. Cornell, undated (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Football v. UConn, undated (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Wrestling, undated (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Poynter Scholarship, undated (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Band, undated (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Freshman Registration, undated (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Football v. Harvard, undated (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Debate?, undated (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Yale person?, undated (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Brown Lacrosse and Basketball, undated (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Harvard/Yale Hockey, undated (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Play of W.W., undated (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Party?, undated (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Blithe Spirit, undated (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Josh, undated (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Yale Daily News ID Photos, undated (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Handball, undated (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Basketball, undated (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Swimming- Army/Yale, undated (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Wrestling vs. Army, undated (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Veeder Phi Gam negs, undated (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Water Polo, undated (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Football v. Dartmouth, undated (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Water Polo negs, undated (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Baseball vs. Harvard, undated (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Big Brothers and Sisters, undated (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Fencing vs. NYU, undated (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Princeton Basketball, undated (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Princeton Football, undated (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Lacrosse mugs, undated (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - V. Basketball vs. Penn, undated (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Rugby vs. Princeton, undated (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Wrestling Head Game, undated (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - NYC Weekend, undated (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - Con Candids, undated (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - Volleyball, undated (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - Misc. gateways, portals, arches, undated (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - YPMB drum major, undated (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - Volleyball, undated (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - TW- Foreign Student, undated (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - Yale Cabaret, undated (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - Yale vs. Vassar women's soccer, undated (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - Women's field hockey vs. Cornell, undated (Box 12, Folder 117)
- Photographs of campus and students by Yale Daily News photographer Richard A. Elbrecht, circa 1953-1955; Accession 2005-A-093
  - Photographs of campus and students by Yale Daily News photographer Richard A. Elbrecht, circa 1953-1955 (Box 1)
- Photographic negatives used in the publication of the Yale Daily News, circa 1950-2001; Accession 2005-A-185
  - 1958-1979 (Box 1)
  - 1961-1983 (Box 2)
  - 1963-1980
    - People (Box 3)
      - A-B (Box 4)
      - B-C (Box 5)
      - D-F (Box 6)
      - F-H (Box 7)
      - H-K (Box 8)
      - K (Box 9)
      - N-S, miscellaneous (Box 10)
      - S-V, 1966-1984 (Box 11)
      - W-Z, assorted, 1966-1984 (Box 12)
  - 1969-1976 (Box 13)
  - 1959-1976 (Box 14)
  - 1971-1984 (Box 15–17)
  - Sports, 1976-1983 (Box 18–19)
  - 1977-1981 (Box 20)
  - Places, 1978-1983 (Box 21)
  - 1979-1987 (Box 22)
  - 1979-1983 (Box 23)
  - 1980-1985 (Box 24)
  - 1983-1989 (Box 25)
  - Sports
    - 1982-1986 (Box 26)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 27)
  - #1, 1984-1985 (Box 28)
  - 1985 Sep -1986 Mar (Box 29)
  - 1984 Sep -1985 May (Box 30)
  - N-Z, 1985-1986 (Box 31)
  - Sports, 1987-1988 (Box 32)
  - The Game, 1981, 1984 (Box 32)
  - #2, Arts, 1984-1985 (Box 33)
  - 1995-1996 (Box 34)
  - 1988-1991 (Box 35)
  - 1992-1996, mostly sports (Box 36)
  - Sports, 1982-1987 (Box 37)
  - Places, A-K, 1991-2000 (Box 38)
  - 1993-1996 (Box 39)
  - 1994-1996 (Box 40)
  - 1992-1996 (Box 41)
  - 1993-1994 (Box 42)
  - Assorted negatives and prints (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous negatives and slides (Box 44)
  - 1991-1995 (Box 45)
  - 1991-1992 (Box 46)
  - 1992-1993 (Box 47)
  - 1995-1997 (Box 48–49)
  - Football (Box 50)
  - Sports, mostly, 1989-1996 (Box 51)
  - 1992-2001 (Box 52)
  - Medium format negatives, circa 1950 (Box 53)
  - 1992-1997 (Box 53)
- Photographs of campus and student life by Yale Daily News photographer Winchell S. Carroll, 1955-1958; Accession 2011-A-046
  Arrangement
  Records are arranged alphabetically.
  Custodial History
  Gift of Winchell S. Carroll, 2011.
  - Negatives
    - Advertisements and publicity
      - "A Touch of the Poet" window advertisement, perhaps on [off] the new building, 1958 September (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Old Tankard Ale and moguls, 1957 January 15 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Quality Gro[cery] ad (2), 1958 September 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Quality Wines ad, 1958 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Reingold girls, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Yale Daily News ad, Sept. 9, Circa 1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Buildings and grounds of Yale and New Haven
      - '56 election polling booth, 1956 November 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Harkness Tower, 1956 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - High schools, 1958 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Hockey rink, 1958 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - New Linear accelerator, 1958 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - New telephone building, 1958 September 7 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Old Campus, Sept. 9, Circa 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Scenes at Yale, 1958 April (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Snow pictures, 1958 March 19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Wright, Durfee, Battell, Law School, Trumbull, 1958 April (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Yale, 1958 April (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Individuals
      - Arnold, Thurman, Feb. 7, Circa 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Campaign button seller outside Yale Station, 1956 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Daley, William (Mory's), 1957 January 8 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Farrell, 1956 December 11 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Gottlieb, Ben (YUK), 1958 May (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Hogan (cross-country captain), 1956 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Oliver, Jordan, 1955 spring (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Scooter cop, Sept. 9, Circa 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Sieden, Steve, WYBC studio 2, 1957 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Walker, 1956 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Organizations and events
      - Class Day officers, 1956 October 23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        General
        Carroll and Ziebarth named as photographers.
      - Political Union (PU) meeting, 1955 Fall (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - WYBC
        - Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
        - Barf [rejects]
          - Loeb, Pete, 1957 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
          - Pell, Louie, 1957 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
          - Real barf, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
        - Crankshaw and Bob Resner, 1957 October 30 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        - Frosh Rally, 1957 September 22 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Yale Sports Car Club Jamboree, 1955 October 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Sports
      - Baseball
        - "Mugs", 1957 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 6)
          Individual portraits of players on the field.
        - U.S. Army, 1955 spring (Box 1, Folder 6)
        - Yale (team in the field), 1958 April (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Basketball
        - Intercollege
          - Timothy Dwight (TD) Colleege, 1958 February 21 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        - Varsity
          - Brown, 1957 December (Box 1, Folder 6)
          - Columbia, 1957 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 6)
          - Fordham, 1957 December 12 (Box 1, Folder 6)
            Final score was Yale 80, Fordham 81.
          - Holy Cross, 1957 December 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
          - NCAA, first round
            - Yale vs. North Carolina, 1957 March 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
            - Other games, 1957 March 4 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Crew
        - Blackwell Cup, 1957 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        - Intercollege, 1958 April (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Football
        - Intercollege
          - Branford vs. Pierson, 1957 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 7)
          - Calhoun vs. Trumbull, 1957 October 14 (Box 1, Folder 7)
          - Championship: Silliman vs. Saybrook, 1956 November 20 (Box 1, Folder 7)
          - Timothy Dwight (TD)
            - Vs. Berkeley, 1957 October (Box 1, Folder 7)
            - Vs. Branford, 1957 October (Box 1, Folder 7)
            - Vs. Leverit House, 1957 November 22 (Box 1, Folder 7)
          - Jonathan Edwards (JE) vs. Davenport, 1957 October 11 (Box 1, Folder 7)
          - Saybrook
            - Vs. J.E., 1957 October 25 (Box 1, Folder 7)
            - Vs. Pierson, 1957 October 10 (Box 1, Folder 7)
              Game ended in scoreless tie.
        - Varsity
          - Columbia, 1956 October 13 (Box 1, Folder 8)
          - Dartmouth, 1956 November 3 (Box 1, Folder 8)
            - Rejects, 1956 November 3 (Box 1, Folder 8)
              Carroll, Ellsworth and Schulz are all credited as photographers.
          - Handsome Dan, 1958 fall (Box 1, Folder 8)
          - Practice, 1958 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 8)
          - Springfield, 1958 September 15 (Box 1, Folder 8)
          - Trinity, 1958 September 13 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Hockey
        - 1957 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 9)
        - Dartmouth, 1957 February 19 (Box 1, Folder 9)
        - Princeton, 1957 February 23 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Lacrosse, Yale frosh vs. Exeter, 1957 April 21 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Rugby, vs. California, 1957 April 21 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Soccer, intercollege, 1957 October 21 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Tennis
        - 1957 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 9)
        - Miami, 1955 spring (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Student life
      - Frisbie match between Pete Smith, Ron Regan, Tom Sargent, George Doty, George Armor, and Bill Ryland, 1957 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Tang Trophy
        - College Weekend, 1957 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        - Trials, 1957 May 3 (Box 1, Folder 10)
          - TD vs. Silliman, 1957 May 3 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Trumbull Beer and Bike Race, 1955 spring (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Unidentified samples, Circa 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbooks
    These are prints of photographs taken by Carroll; some are accompanied by clippings of articles in which images were published.
    - First semester,sophomore year; first semester as a board member, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Second semester, sophomore year; second semester as a board member, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - First semester, junior year; third semester as a board member, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Second semester, junior year; fourth semester as a board member, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - First semester, part 1, senior year; fifth and last semester as a board member, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - First semester, part 2, senior year; fourth [fifth and last] semester as a board member, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Second semester, senior year; now no longer member of the board technically. Senior Board returns at midyears., 1958 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 1958 April-June (Box 4, Folder 1)
      This volume also contains programs, invitations and other memorabilia documenting senior class activities and graduation, as well as invoices, membership cards, photographs, and correspondence documenting Carroll's senior year.
    - 1958 fall (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Slides
    - Buildings and grounds of Yale and New Haven
      - Campus
        - 1955 (Box 5, Folder 1)
        - 1957 October (Box 5, Folder 1)
        - Scenes, 1958 February 10, May (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Individuals
      - Hertzfeld, Hal, TD 1958, 1956 June (Box 5, Folder 2)
        In jail in Summerset, PA after being arrested for speeding during trip home to Toledo.
      - McCarthur, Jan, Yale Drama School 1958 graduate, Circa 1958 (Box 5, Folder 2)
        The original lady whose fingers did the walking through the Yellow Pages advertisements.
      - Truman, Harry, on morning walk while at TD, 1958 April
    - Organizations and events
      - College Weekend, 1958 May 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
        Includes one slide of Carroll with Brenda, dated 19 April 1958.
      - TD production of "Stalag 17", 1958 May 7 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Sports
      - Amateur Athletic Union (AAU) swim meet, 1958 April 3 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Basketball vs. Columbia, 1958 February 21 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Crew, TD, 1958 April 18 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Football
        - Intercollege, TD
          - Vs. Branford, 1957 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 4)
          - Vs. Trumbull, 1957 October 3 (Box 5, Folder 4)
        - Varsity
          - Brown, 1955 November (Box 5, Folder 5)
          - Colgate, 1957 October 26 (Box 5, Folder 5)
          - Princeton, 1955 November (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Hockey vs. Middlebury, 1958 February 26 (Box 5, Folder 5)